Nice serve, Yuki!
Right on!
Thank you very much.
Yuki looks good no matter what she's doing.
I can't believe she's the same age as us, man.
Yuki got another service ace!
She's so cool!
They've seen nothing yet. When Ms. Yuki
gets serious, she's on a whole other level.
She's beautiful, smart, and athletic...
I can't see how she's related
to Hitoyoshi at all!
Well, I can't say I disagree, but...
I'm still feeling the high
from the movie-like experience I had
where Ms. Yuki's life was in danger.
She was a ruthless murderer...
The fourth of the Dragon's Nine:
Xue the White Wolf.
I won't kill anyone anymore.
And I won't let anyone die
because of me, either!
Dragon's Nine      Assassination
I still have far too many unanswered questions.
But as Ms. Yuki continues in
her pursuit of normalcy...
What?!
Stare
She's doing the best she can!
I won't let their jealousy and envy...
Stare
get to me!
Hey, Hitoyoshi!
Oh, man! That was a close one.
We'd be in big trouble if you
got hurt now, wouldn't we?
Especially with you-know-who.
It's not just because of Ms. Yuki
that I'm being singled out right now.
Grin
She's a big part of it, too.
Episode 6: You're Lonelier Than I Thought.
How can I help you, Ms. Nitta?
Oh, don't be like that.
It wouldn't kill you to be a little nicer
to helpless new teachers like myself,
Hitoyoshi.
You're way too close!
Haven't you heard of personal space?!
Jealousy
And the reason why things have
become so complicated is...
I'm here!
Meow
Who are you?!
Oh, come on.
How could you have already forgotten me
after the passionate night we shared?
It's me, Grace.
The setup here is that I'm
the new gym teacher, Ms. Nitta—
a big-sister figure related to you—
who's just moved to Tokyo.
The way you look and talk
is completely different!
And that's way too many details!
If Xue's specialty is "combat,"
mine is "espionage."
I'm especially good at disguises.
Besides, this is the real me.
Or do you prefer girls with long, dark hair?
Just like your "Ms. Yuki."
What?! No, that's not...
It's written all over your face!
You're a funny guy.
I thought you'd had enough,
but do you still have business with me?
You know, I just love having fun.
The legendary assassin, the great Xue,
now serving under a civilian brat
and saying that she's given up
killing on top of that...
I'd never find anything that amusing
if I fled to the tropics!
With that said, I have no intention of killing,
and even less of being killed myself.
In other words, my hostility level is zero.
Of course, I'm not asking for you
to trust me for nothing in return.
Let's negotiate.
A negotiation between assassins...
First of all, I'll no longer make any move
on you or Hitoyoshi with killing intent.
And furthermore...
I knew it! Is she about to offer untold riches
or super-secret info to sweeten the deal?!
For three months, I'll provide you
with bread from the school store!
What, bread?! That's such
a commoner thing to say...
No, maybe it's some kind
of secret assassin code?!
Of course, I'm not just talking about any
ordinary bread here. What I'm offering...
is Katsuda Bread! That's right,
all the Katsuda Bread you can eat!
I'm in.
Oh, she's in.
We have a deal!
Ms. Yuki?!
Are you sure about this?
There's no need to worry.
It's strictly prohibited for us to kill
an ordinary person without cause.
And now that she understands
she is no match for me,
she has nothing to gain from
harming you, Master Hitoyoshi.
However, even if something
like that were to happen,
I will protect... you...
Wipe that drool, please.
And besides, I can handle second-rate
killers like her by the thousands.
There is no need for concern.
Yeah?
Dang... I've been downgraded to fodder tier.
Well, anyway,
I'll continue to observe you guys
quietly, so let's get along, okay?
Or at least, that was the plan, but...
Truth be told, I never
really liked gym class myself.
But I figured the easiest jobs to slack
off during were this and school nurse.
Weren't you going to observe us quietly?
Aren't I whispering to you right now?
Not right into my ear, please!
Besides...
I think it's actually bothering her.
Yuki!
Are you gonna serve or not?
Right! My apologies!
Are you sure she's not just worried
about you pulling something funny again?
You didn't notice, huh?
Notice what?
Oh, nothing really.
But, since you're the one asking...
I'll tell you
everything.
Wha...
Now I've done it...
Oh...
That was amazing, Yuki!
It went straight through the net!
You're incredible!
Just who are you, really?
You want to join our club?!
Well... Um...
I...
I-I really messed up.
Well, I know it wasn't your fault.
But... What happened, all of a sudden?
I'm not certain myself.
I understand that Grace
doesn't wish you harm, but...
Whenever I see you with
someone else from the underworld,
I feel this sense of alienation
for some reason.
Is this, too, part of being normal?
Or is there...
something wrong with me?
You didn't notice, huh?
Didn't notice, huh?
Ms. Yuki Feeling Jealousy
For The First Time
Um, it's normal to feel that way.
It's normal?
Master Hitoyoshi?!
Mornin'...
Master Hitoyoshi!
The towel is...
The towel is fluffy!
Nice!
It's been a month since she started
training to wash towels.
One time, she mixed colored
and white towels together.
Another, she put in dishwashing soap
instead of laundry detergent.
She even forgot to take out
the tissues before washing.
She's overcome so many failures.
You finally succeeded at doing the laundry!
You've come so far, Ms. Yuki!
Yes!
You're happy for her, too, aren't ya, Mochita?
It's so warm.
I'm going to go fold it.
Yokoya
Let's see.
What should we have for dinner tonight?
Dinner...
The only thing we have in
the fridge is cabbage, isn't it?
Cabbage...
Slicing...
Sliced cabbage...
And next to the sliced cabbage
would be tonkatsu—
or rather, we would need to reserve a space
for Katsuda's Sauce! Don't you agree?
Katsuda's Sauce
Mrs. Fuku, two tonkatsu, please!
You got it.
Katsuda Side Dish Store
Thank you as always.
They're almost done frying,
so could you wait a moment?
Sorry 'bout that.
Sure.
By the way...
Who's that beauty with you?
Master Hitoyoshi.
Th-There's Katsuda's Sauce...
There's so many boxes
filled with Katsuda's Sauce!
Oh, um... She's a maid who's
been working for us...
So this is the birthplace of Katsuda's Sauce...
I'm so moved!
I kinda know the feeling.
You have moments where you feel
this way, as well, Master Hitoyoshi?
Yeah. Like when I went to see
a hero show a long time ago.
Garden Park
Hero Show!
You can't help but feel your heart stir when
you see something you love, you know?
That's normal.
Normal...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The tonkatsu's ready. You want it cut, right?
Oh, yes, please.
Look, Master Hitoyoshi!
Though his hands tremble with age,
enough to make holding a blade dangerous...
The moment he slices through the tonkatsu,
the tremors stop, and he wields his
weapon with the utmost precision.
I didn't expect him to cut it
so evenly at that age.
What kind of training has he undergone?
Could he be one of us?
I-Is he the legendary assassin
who is known to reside in Japan?!
She's fangirling hard.
Hm? What's wrong?
O-Oh, nothing. It's just, our maid is a
huge fan of Katsuda's Sauce. Right?
I see, I see. I'm glad to hear that.
I'm the one who makes the sauce, you see.
So you are the god behind this miracle!
Well, my husband came up with the recipe.
I just produce it, sorry to say.
Katsuda's Sauce is super popular, you know!
Your fried dishes are so
crispy and amazing, too!
Is that so? Thank you.
U-Um, I... I wanted to thank you.
Thank me?
Until recently, I'd never considered meals to
be something that could be delicious or fun.
But the moment that sauce touched my tongue,
my whole world changed.
You may think I'm exaggerating,
but it really was that important to me.
When I taste that sauce,
words can't express how I feel.
I feel a warmth deep inside my heart.
That's why... Please allow me
once again to say...
Please accept my heartfelt thanks
and respect, Mrs. Fuku Katsuda.
Ms. Maid, was it?
Yes.
Are you happy right now, Ms. Maid?
Happy?
The warmth you're feeling
is that of happiness.
And it might be because of
the happiness you feel now
that you were able to realize
how delicious the sauce is.
I can't know for sure, though.
Sorry 'bout that.
The warmth...
Yes... I think you might be right.
Hey, little miss.
You had a little lint on your shoulder.
On your shoulder, y'see.
He was able to... sneak up behind me?
As I thought, Master Katsuda...
is no ordinary man!
Speaking of which, we have
some freshly made sauce.
You want a taste?
What?
Y-Yes, by all means!
Just a little...
Master Hitoyoshi...
The sauce... It's yummy. The sauce...
Glad to hear it.
Yokoya
Thank you for the meal.
I'll handle the washing up, so please
get some rest, Master Hitoyoshi.
Okay, thank you.
How should I put it...
When I see how happy Ms. Yuki is now,
it's hard to believe she was once
one of the most powerful assassins...
Dragon's Nine      Assassination
Dragon's Nine
The Dragon's Nine is a Chinese legend that
refers to nine children born of a dragon.
Each child had a different form and personality,
and each resided in a place that best suited
their nature, but none could ever become
a dragon like their parent.
As I expected, the only results
are about Chinese folklore.
Sh-Should I just ask Ms. Yuki herself?
Oh, but...
she might have reasons
to not want to talk about it.
And, besides that...
Though she may have tried
to put her painful past behind her,
it might not be something
she can so easily forget.
I wouldn't want to reawaken any trauma.
It'd be best if I waited for Ms. Yuki
to share her past with me.
Probably.
And yet, I still want to know more about her.
Yoshi... Hitoyoshi...
We can see each other anytime, okay?
I'm sorry. It's my fault that
things are the way they are.
I have to go, okay, Hitoyoshi?
Don't go, Mom!
We'll see each other soon, Hitoyoshi.
Don't leave me, Mom! Mom!
Master Hitoyoshi.
Are you all right?
You were groaning, so I came to check on you.
You suddenly fell towards me,
so I caught you at once, but...
S-Sorry!
I was kinda... having a weird dream, and...
Were you dreaming of your mother again?
Y-Yeah...
If that's the case,
how about resting your head on my lap?
You're real fond of that one!
Nope! I'm already wide awake, so I'm good!
What's this...
Huh... Oh!
You were researching the Dragon's Nine?
Yeah.
Are you curious about them?
J-Just a little!
I was just thinking I didn't know
much about you, so...
That's true. Well, as for the Dragon's Nine...
To tell you the truth, I don't know
that much about them either.
I was taken in by my mentor
and brought into the clan,
but even after joining, all I did
was follow my mentor's orders.
I've only even laid eyes on
a few of the other members,
and I never found out their names or had
the opportunity to speak with any of them.
It's not that she doesn't want to talk,
but that she just doesn't know, huh?
Unlike now, back then it was all
I could do just to stay alive,
so I had little interest in other people.
I started to lose sight of what
I was doing and why I was doing it.
My only worry was being abandoned
for disappointing my mentor.
That's why I still haven't grown
accustomed to all this yet.
The birds chirping, the sunlight shining
through the gaps in the curtains...
They're all such little things in life,
but they sparkle so brilliantly to me.
I can't get over how wondrous it all is.
Katsuda's Sauce
Sometimes I feel like I'm still dreaming,
and I just haven't woken up yet.
That's how brightly this world shines for me.
But when I see your face, Master Hitoyoshi,
I'm able to remind myself that right now,
I'm just a girl learning how to be normal.
I'm looking forward to the day when this
lifestyle becomes second nature to me.
That's when I'll truly be able
to call myself normal.
M-Me, too!
Every morning when I see
your face, I feel at ease.
It made me really happy
that after everything that happened,
you still chose to stay here.
That's why I wanted to get to know you more.
So, uh, anyway...
Thank you so much...
for coming... here.
Of course.
Then I'll tell you something new about me.
The reason I love having you
rest your head on my lap...
is because it reminds me of the very first
time I was able to do something for you.
So whenever you have another bad dream,
I'll always be here to lend you my lap.
Um... That's... Never mind.
Thanks. I'd love to.
Then I'll tell you something about me, too.
The truth is, the dream I had just now
wasn't really a bad one, exactly.
What kind of dream was it?
Instead of my mom,
I had a dream about a hero
coming to get me, I guess.